Kristian Ivancevic

A.B.Krcelica 17,10290 Zapresic,Croatia

Cell. + 385 97 6254-232, E-mail: kristian697ivancevic@gmail.com

EDUCATION

High School

09/2006-06/2011 IT and computer technician

I. tehnička škola Tesla, Zagreb (Croatia)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Currently unemployed – learning IT skills (front end web development) from home (html,css,js,react.js,next.js), taking time off from traveling last few years

Order Picker Conglom Inc Richmond, BC, 13180 Mitchell Road, Unit 120 April 2019 – May 2019

My main tasks were:

- Recieve and check incoming orders to pick
- Locate products using information on order
- Build pallets with orders and position them to loading docks
- Wrap orders before loading truck
- Re-stock inventory manually or with warehouse equipment
- Keep records of completed order
- Maintain equipment and report on malfunctions
- Cleaning floor
- -Learned how to operate standing forklift (don't have licence but know how to operate with him very well)

Order Picker Bruce & Clark Richmond, BC, 6691 Elmbridge way, Unit 110 February 2019 – April 2019

- Locate products using information on order
- Build pallets with orders and position them to loading docks
- Wrap orders before loading truck
- Re-stock inventory manually or with warehouse equipment
- Keep records of completed order
- Maintain equipment and report on malfunctions

- Cleaning floor

Order Picker

Conglom Inc (work through recruitment agency AngusOne) Richmond, BC, 13180 Mitchell Road, Unit 120 July 2018 – January 2019

My main tasks were:

- Recieve and check incoming orders to pick
- Locate products using information on order
- Build pallets with orders and position them to loading docks
- Wrap orders before loading truck
- Re-stock inventory manually or with warehouse equipment
- Keep records of completed order
- Maintain equipment and report on malfunctions
- Cleaning floor
- -Learned how to operate standing forklift (don't have licence but know how to operate with him very well)

Barista

Sodexo Ltd

Dublin, eBay, Atrium Building, Navan Road March 2018 – May 2018

My main tasks were:

- Communicating and servicing customers
- Making sure my workplace is clean and tidy
- Preparing coffee, tea, and all sort of drinks
- Food serving
- -Making sandwiches, salads, smoothies

Catering Assistant

Abargrove Ltd

Dublin, Shelbourne Park, Greyhound stadium July 2017 – December 2017

My main tasks were:

- Catering
- Cleaning tables
- Communicating and servicing customers
- Polishing cutlery

Catering Assistant

Dublin, Artane Castle Shopping Centre, Artane& The Square Tallaght June 2017 – February 2018

My main tasks were:

- Serving food
- Cleaning tables and tray
- Sorting dirty glasses, plates, cup, cleaning and washing them
- Communicating and servicing customers
- Polishing cutlery

Deliverer

DHL, Hamburg/Munchen (Germany)

September 2016 – April 2017

My main tasks were:

- Working with scanner
- Sorting packets depending on streets you have on your tour plane and priority
- Delivering to receiver
- Communicating and servicing customers
- Knowing your tour plane

Waiter, bartender, barista, barkeeper

Beerhouse Mali Medo - d.o.o., Zagreb (Croatia)

June/2016-Semptember/2016

Beerhouse with home-brewed beer and domestic food located in the center of Zagreb, in the street called "Tkalča" which is known as the most famous touristic street in Zagreb. I had an opportunity to learn about active sales.

My main tasks were:

- Communication and service to guests
- Reservation acceptance
- Inventur
- Keeping the club clean
- Good order
- Sorting and counting money
- Working in team
- Shiftwork
- Working in the bar

Managing Director

Elisa Trgovina d.o.o., Zagreb (Croatia)

October 2014 - May 2016

Company engage in the sale of outdoor equipment in most visited Shopping Mall (Arena Centar – Zagreb)

My main tasks were:

- Employment of workers
- Work on the cash desk
- Sales of products
- Communicating and servicing customers
- Working in team
- Inventur
- Receipt of goods
- Calculation of the proceeds
- -Receiving complaints

Shop salesperson

Muller d.o.o., Zagreb – West Gate (CROATIA)

November 2013 - December 2013

My tasks were:

- Sales of products
- Work with customers
- Goods receipt
- Inventur
- Work in warehouse

Warehouse worker April 2013 – October 2013 Orbico d.o.o., Zagreb (CROATIA)

My tasks were:

- Loading and unloading good from trucks
- Sorting products
- Stocktaking of warehouse

FOREIGN LANGUAGES

English (fluent)

SKILL

IT Skills:

Comprehensive knowledge of Microsoft Office tools (Word, Excel, PowerPoint) and various Web Browsers

Communication skills:

Excellent communication skills gained in more than 7 years of experience in working with people. I am an openminded person ready for adapting in a new multicultural environment.

Job-related skills:

With my experience I can work in various industries. I am ready to learn and work in retail, sales, hospitality and administration.

ADDITIONAL INFO

About me:

I am 27 years old and I come from Croatia. I have graduated Computer technician and IT high school in Zagreb - Croatia. My goal is to find a full-time job that suits my preferences, knowledge, and skills, through which I will better my experience and advance my career. I am a very communicative and goal motivated individual who is able to work both in a team and alone.

ABLE TO START IMMEDIATELY.